



{
    "services": ["Pricing Models", "Interchange plus pricing", "Pass-through cost", "Recurring Payments", "Suscriptions", "Payment plans", "Virtual Terminal", "Customizable Reports", "Advanced System Tracker", "IVR Payments", "Payment Pages", "SMS Payments", "Email Payments", "Point-of-Sale (Clover)", "Payment Hardware", "Payment Method", "Cahs Managment", "Debit & Credit Card Payments", "ACH Payments", "Customer Manager", "Faster Deposits", "Fraud Management Tools", "3D Secure", "Chargeback Advanced Module", "Chargeback dispute view", "Transaction Risk Score", "Professional Accounting Services", "Company Registration", "Payroll", "Bookeeping", "Business assessment", "Branding and E-Commerce Development"], 
    "companyName": "GYB Connect", 
    "commonQuestions": [
        {"answer": "We offer Interchange plus pricing and pass-through cost pricing models to suit your business needs.", "question": "What pricing models do you offer?"}, 
        {"answer": "We support debit & credit cards, ACH payments, and cash management solutions.", "question": "What payment methods do you support?"}, {"answer": "Yes, we offer solutions for recurring payments, subscriptions, and payment plans.", "question": "Do you offer recurring billing solutions?"}, {"answer": "We provide customizable reports to help you track your payments and finances.", "question": "What kind of reporting do you provide?"}, {"answer": "Our fraud management tools include 3D Secure, a chargeback advanced module, and a chargeback dispute view.", "question": "What fraud management tools do you offer?"}, {"answer": "We provide a chargeback dispute view, alerting you within 24-48 hours of a potential chargeback.", "question": "How do you handle chargebacks?"}, {"answer": "We serve various industries, including legal offices, jewelry, healthcare, and retail.", "question": "What industries do you serve?"}, {"answer": "Yes, we offer Point-of-Sale solutions through Clover.", "question": "Do you offer point-of-sale solutions?"}, {"answer": "We provide professional accounting services such as company registration, payroll, bookkeeping, and business assessment.", "question": "What accounting services do you provide?"}, {"answer": "Yes, we offer branding and e-commerce development services.", "question": "Do you offer e-commerce development services?"}, {"answer": "We use Transaction Risk Score from ipqualityscore.com to assess transaction risk.", "question": "What is your transaction risk score?"}, {"answer": "Yes, we offer a virtual terminal for processing payments online.", "question": "Do you have a virtual terminal?"}, {"answer": "We offer faster deposit options for your convenience.", "question": "How fast are deposits?"}, {"answer": "Yes, we offer both SMS and email payment options.", "question": "Do you offer SMS and email payment options?"}]}